Kheel, Theodore W. Books and Articles 6021/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A Natural Way of Business, 2006; Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: A Natural Way of Business: Group Punta Cana: An Unusual Partnership in Sustainable Tourism, 2006; Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Author: Kathleen Gupta; Udayan Gupta; William Jefferson Clinton; David Lane; Jake Kheel
    Notes: How Frank Rainieri, Theodore Kheel, Oscar De La Renta, and Julio Inglesias Helped Transform an Island Economy
  - Item 2: A Natural Way of Business: Group Punta Cana: An Unusual Partnership in Sustainable Tourism, 2006; Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Notes: How Frank Rainieri, Theodore Kheel, Oscar De La Renta, and Julio Inglesias Helped Transform an Island Economy. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: A Natural Way of Business: Group Punta Cana: An Unusual Partnership in Sustainable Tourism, 2006; Publication (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Notes: How Frank Rainieri, Theodore Kheel, Oscar De La Renta, and Julio Inglesias Helped Transform an Island Economy. Copy 3.
- A New Nation Emerges, 1957; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A New Nation Emerges, 1957; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Author: New York Herald Tribune
    Notes: Reprinted from New York Herald Tribune, March 6, 1957
  - Item 2: A New Nation Emerges, 1957; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Notes: Reprinted from New York Herald Tribune, March 6, 1957. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: A New Nation Emerges, 1957; Publication (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Notes: Reprinted from New York Herald Tribune, March 6, 1957. Copy 3.
- The New York Botanical Garden, 1991; Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The New York Botanical Garden: An Illustrated Chronicle of Plants and People, 1991; Publication (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Author: Ogden Tanner; Adele Auchincloss; Allen Rokach
- New York City, 1979; Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: New York City, 1979; Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Author: Business Marketing Corporation for New York City
    Notes: Includes handwritten letter on cover from Marty Evans. Also includes "The Manahattan Project/2" from the Alternative Institute.
  - Item 2: New York City, 1979; Publication (Box 8, Folder 11)
- New York Strike Mediator Urges Bargaining Reforms, 1963; Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: New York Strike Mediator Urges Bargaining Reforms, 1963; Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Author: Philip N. Schuyler
    Notes: Published in Editor and Publisher, v.96:no.16 (1963:Apr. 20)
  - Item 2: New York Strike Mediator Urges Bargaining Reforms, 1963; Publication (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Notes: Published in Editor and Publisher, v.96:no.16 (1963:Apr. 20). Copy 2.
- The One Hundred and Seventy-Ninth Annual, 2004; Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The One Hundred and Seventy-Ninth Annual: An Invitational Exhibition of Contemporary American Art, 2004; Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Author: National Academy
  - Item 2: The One Hundred and Seventy-Ninth Annual: An Invitational Exhibition of Contemporary American Art, 2004; Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: The One Hundred and Seventy-Ninth Annual: An Invitational Exhibition of Contemporary American Art, 2004; Publication (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Operating Manual for Spaceship Earth, 1978; Publication (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Operating Manual for Spaceship Earth, 1978; Publication (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Author: R. Buckminster Fuller
- The Oral History Collection of Columbia University, 1973; Publication (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Oral History Collection of Columbia University, 1973; Publication (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Author: Elizabeth B. Mason; Louis M. Starr
- Organized Labor in American History, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Organized Labor in American History, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Author: Philip Taft; Theodore W. Kheel
    Notes: Book review by Theodore Kheel
  - Item 2: Organized Labor in American History, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Notes: Book review by Theodore Kheel. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Organized Labor in American History, 1964; Publication (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Notes: Book review by Theodore Kheel. Copy 3.
- A Partnership Between PERC and ICR, Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: A Partnership Between PERC and ICR, Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Author: Foundation for Prevention and Early Resolution of Conflict; Institute on Conflict Resolution
  - Item 2: A Partnership Between PERC and ICR, Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: A Partnership Between PERC and ICR, Publication (Box 8, Folder 17)
- The Party After You Left, 2004; Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Party After You Left, 2004; Publication (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Author: Roz Chast
- Pathway to Tomorrow: The Impact of Automation on People, 1967; Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Pathway to Tomorrow: The Impact of Automation on People, 1967; Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Author: Trevor Evans; Margaret Stewart
    Notes: International Conference on Automation, Full Employment and a Balanced Economy, Rome, June 1967.
  - Item 2: Pathway to Tomorrow: The Impact of Automation on People, 1967; Publication (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Notes: International Conference on Automation, Full Employment and a Balanced Economy, Rome, June 1967. Copy 2.
- Permanent Missions to the United Nations, 1993; Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Permanent Missions to the United Nations, 1993; Publication (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Author: United Nations
- Personal Privacy in an Information Society, 1977; Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Personal Privacy in an Information Society, 1977; Publication (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Author: Privacy Protection Study Commission
    Notes: Report of the Privacy Protection Commission
- A Plan for Labor-Management Peace in New York City, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A Plan for Labor-Management Peace in New York City, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: Prepared at the request of Abraham D. Beame
  - Item 2: A Plan for Labor-Management Peace in New York City, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: Prepared at the request of Abraham D. Beame. Copy 2.
- Play Production in the High School, 1968; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Play Production in the High School, 1968; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Author: Roy A. Beck; William E. Buys; Daniel Fleischhacker; Russell J. Grandstaff; J. Thomas Sill
- Points for Consideration by the Governor's Conferencee on Public Employment Relations, Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Points for Consideration by the Governor's Conferencee on Public Employment Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Points for Consideration by the Governor's Conferencee on Public Employment Relations, 1968; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Population, the Planet, and the Press, 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Population, the Planet, and the Press, 1985; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
    Author: Dick MacDonald; Rafael M. Salas; Thomas Burch; Joel Gregory; Sigurd Hennum; Lester Brown; Anthony Westell; Bruce Halliday; Colin Godbold
- Populi, 1993; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Populi, 1993; Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Author: United Nation Population Fund
    Notes: v.17:no.3 (1990:Sep.)
- The Port Authority 1962 Covenant: Bar to Mass Transportation, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Port Authority 1962 Covenant: Bar to Mass Transportation, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Author: Robert J. Kheel; Theodore W. Kheel
    Notes: Reprint from Rutgers Law Review, v.27:no.1 (1973:Fall)
  - Item 2: The Port Authority 1962 Covenant: Bar to Mass Transportation, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Notes: Reprint from Rutgers Law Review, v.27:no.1 (1973:Fall). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Port Authority 1962 Covenant: Bar to Mass Transportation, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Notes: Reprint from Rutgers Law Review, v.27:no.1 (1973:Fall). Copy 3.
- The Practical Limits of Arbitration in the Settlement of Collective Bargaining Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Practical Limits of Arbitration in the Settlement of Collective Bargaining Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Notes: Reprint from the proceedings of the Southern Legal Foundation 17th Annual Institute on Labor Law
  - Item 2: The Practical Limits of Arbitration in the Settlement of Collective Bargaining Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Notes: Reprint from the proceedings of the Southern Legal Foundation 17th Annual Institute on Labor Law. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Practical Limits of Arbitration in the Settlement of Collective Bargaining Disputes, 1971; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Notes: Reprint from the proceedings of the Southern Legal Foundation 17th Annual Institute on Labor Law. Copy 3.
- The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1961; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Notes: Prepared for the New York Chamber of Commerce
  - Item 2: The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1961; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Notes: Prepared for the New York Chamber of Commerce. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1961; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Notes: Prepared for the New York Chamber of Commerce. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: The Pros and Cons of Compulsory Arbitration, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
    Notes: A Debate Manual
- Psychology Today: An Introduction, 1970; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Psychology Today: An Introduction, 1970; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Author: CRM Books
- Public Employee Unionism in Israel, 1971; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Public Employee Unionism in Israel, 1971; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Author: Jerome Lefkowitz
- The Public Interest, 1969; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Public Interest, 1969; Publication (Box 9, Folder 11)
    Author: Edward Banfield; Daniel Bell; Nathan Glazer; David Gordon; Virginia Held; Irving Kristol; Dick Netzer; George Sternlieb; Paul Weaver; James Q. Wilson
    Notes: no.16 (1969:Summer)
- The Public Interest, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Public Interest, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Author: Irving Kristol; Marc J. Roberts; Harry Brill; Lester C. Thurow; Richard Scobie; Roger Starr; James Tobin; Peter Berger; Nathan Keyfitz; Nathan Glazer
    Notes: no.31 (1973:Spring)
  - Item 2: The Public Interest, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Notes: no.31 (1973:Spring). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Public Interest, 1973; Publication (Box 9, Folder 12)
    Author: Martin Feldstein; Peter F. Drucker; Martin Rein; Hugh Heclo; Aaron Wildavsky; Richard A. Posner; Lester C. Thurow
    Notes: no.33 (1973:Fall)
- The Public Interest, 1974; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The Public Interest, 1974; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Author: Eli Ginzberg; Robert M. Solow; Andrew F. Brimmer; Anthony Downs; Charles V. Hamilton; Herbert E. Klarman; Robert J. Lampman; Lance Liebman; Edmund S. Phelps; Gilbert Y. Steiner; Ralph W. Tyler; Lloyd Ulman
    Notes: no.34 (1974:Winter)
  - Item 2: The Public Interest, 1974; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Author: Robert Martinson; Brigette Berger; Paul H. Weaver; Daniel J. Elazar; Robert Nisbet; Thomas Sowell
    Notes: no.35 (1974:Spring)
  - Item 3: The Public Interest, 1974; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Author: Edward Jay Epstein; Jerome T. Murphy; David K. Cohn; Gordon Tullock; Steven Kelman; Jeffrey O'Connell; Jess Marcum; Henry Rowen
    Notes: no.36 (1974:Summer)
  - Item 4: The Public Interest, 1974; Publication (Box 9, Folder 13)
    Author: Irving Kristol; Daniel Bell; Marc F. Plattner; B. Bruce-Briggs; Nathan Glazer; John McAdams
    Notes: no.37 (1974:Fall)
- The Public Interest, 1975; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Public Interest, 1975; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: David A. Stockman; Jude Wanniski; William C. Baer; Edward Jay Epstein; James Q. Wilson; Nathan Glazer; David A. Musto
    Notes: no.39 (1975:Spring)
  - Item 2: The Public Interest, 1975; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: Leon R. Kass; Martin Feldstein; Nathan Glazer; Brigetter Berger; Carolyn Shaw Bell; Marc F. Plattner; B. Bruce-Briggs
    Notes: no.40 (1975:Summer)
  - Item 3: The Public Interest, 1975; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Item 4: The Public Interest, 1975; Publication (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Author: Robert Nisbet; Martin Diamond; Nathan Glazer; Irving Kristol; Samuel P. Huntington; James Q. Wilson; Aaron Wildavsky; Daniel Bell; Daniel Patrick Moynihan
    Notes: no.41 (1975:Fall)
- The Public Interest, 1976; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The Public Interest, 1976; Publication (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Author: Thomas Sowell; J. S. Fuerst; James Q. Wilson; Seymour Martin Lipset; James S. Coleman; Edgar K. Browning; Bradley R. Schiller
    Notes: no.33 (1976:spring)
- Qualitat Der Regionalentwicklung: Der Fall New York, 1972; Publication (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Qualitat Der Regionalentwicklung: Der Fall New York, 1972; Publication (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Notes: Reprint form Aufgabe Zukunft Qualitat des Lebens, 11. bis. 14 (1972:Apr.)
    Language: German.
- The Racial Revolution in Advertising, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Racial Revolution in Advertising: A True Portrait of America, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Author: Mayor's Committee on Job Advancement
    Notes: How advertiser, agencies, Mayor Wagner's Committee on Job Advancement and other organizations have initiated an all-out attempt to correct the distorted picture of American life.
  - Item 2: The Racial Revolution in Advertising: A True Portrait of America, Publication (Box 9, Folder 17)
    Notes: How advertiser, agencies, Mayor Wagner's Committee on Job Advancement and other organizations have initiated an all-out attempt to correct the distorted picture of American life. Copy 2.
- The Real Voice, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Real Voice, 1964; Publication (Box 9, Folder 18)
    Author: Richard Harris
    Notes: Advance copy. To be published August 17, 1964.
- The Record of the Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 2001; Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Record of the Association of the Bar of the City of New York, 2001; Publication (Box 9, Folder 19)
    Author: Eric H. Holder; Committee on Uniform State Laws; Committee on Civil Rights; Committee on Corrections
    Notes: v.56:no.4 (2001:Fall): Electronic Business and Cybersignatures
- Removing Obstacles to Automation, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Removing Obstacles to Automation, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Author: Margaret Stewart
    Notes: Report of a conference, May 7-9, 1965.
  - Item 2: Removing Obstacles to Automation, 1965; Publication (Box 9, Folder 20)
    Notes: Report of a conference, May 7-9, 1965. Copy 2.
- Report and Determination in the Matter of Christo: The Gates, 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Report and Determination in the Matter of Christo: The Gates, 1981; Publication (Box 9, Folder 21)
    Author: Gordon J. Davis
- Report of the Human Rights Committee, 1992; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Report of the Human Rights Committee, 1992; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Author: Human Rights Committee
    Notes: Forty-seventh Session, Supplement no.40
- Report of Theodore Kheel to Vice President Johnson, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Report of Theodore Kheel to Vice President Johnson, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report of Theodore Kheel to Vice President Johnson, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Report on the Government Program Against Discrimination, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report on the Government Program Against Discrimination, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: Labor Report Bulletin no.8 (1962:Aug. 30)
  - Item 2: Report on the Government Program Against Discrimination, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: Labor Report Bulletin no.8 (1962:Aug. 30). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Report on the Government Program Against Discrimination, 1962; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: Labor Report Bulletin no.8 (1962:Aug. 30). Copy 3.
- A Report to Mayor Lindsay on a Plan for the Survival of Mass Transportation, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Report to Mayor Lindsay on a Plan for the Survival of Mass Transportation, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Notes: For New York City, Yonkers, Newark, Jersey City and Surrounding Areas
  - Item 2: A Report to Mayor Lindsay on a Plan for the Survival of Mass Transportation, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Notes: For New York City, Yonkers, Newark, Jersey City and Surrounding Areas. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: A Report to Mayor Lindsay on a Plan for the Survival of Mass Transportation, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Notes: For New York City, Yonkers, Newark, Jersey City and Surrounding Areas. Copy 3.
- Report to the Department of Transportation, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Report to the Department of Transportation: Collective Bargaining and Mass Transit Subsidies, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Report to the President, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Report to the President of the United States, 1963; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
- The Robert Wood Foundation Annual Report, 1980; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Robert Wood Foundation Annual Report 1980, 1981; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Robert Wood Johnson Foundation
    Notes: January 1, 1980 through December 31, 1980.
- Role of Collective Bargaining in Community Conflict, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Role of Collective Bargaining in Community Conflict, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Notes: No author listed: believed to be Theodore W. Kheel. Draft for "Monthly Labor Review".
  - Item 2: Role of Collective Bargaining in Community Conflict, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Notes: No author listed: believed to be Theodore W. Kheel. Draft for "Monthly Labor Review". Copy 2.
- A Round-Heeld Woman, 2003; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A Round-Heeld Woman: My Late-Life Adventures in Sex and Romance, 2003; Publication (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Author: Jane Juska
- Seeds of Hope, 2002; Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Seeds of Hope: A Message From Young Voices in the Aftermath of September 11., 2002; Publication (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Author: Monica M. Westin; Jessica Lundgren
- Segal, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Segal, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Author: Sidney Janis Gallery
    Notes: Catalogue of George Segal sculpture and bas-relief
  - Item 2: Segal, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Notes: Catalogue of George Segal sculpture and bas-relief. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Segal, 1974; Publication (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Notes: Catalogue of George Segal sculpture and bas-relief. Copy 3.
- The Slow Food Guide to New York City, 2003; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Slow Food Guide to New York City: Restaurants, Markets, Bars, 2003; Publication (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Author: Patrick Martins; Ben Watson
- Social Register, 1979; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Social Register, 1979; Publication (Box 10, Folder 13)
    Author: The Social Register Association
    Notes: v.93 (1978:Nov.)
- Some Observations on the Labor Scene, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Some Observations on the Labor Scene, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Proceedings of the New York University Twenty-Fourth Annual Conference on Labor
  - Item 2: Some Observations on the Labor Scene, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Proceedings of the New York University Twenty-Fourth Annual Conference on Labor. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Some Observations on the Labor Scene, 1972; Publication (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Notes: Reprinted from the Proceedings of the New York University Twenty-Fourth Annual Conference on Labor. Copy 3.
- Soule Food, 1970; Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Soule Food, 1970; Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Notes: Letter to the Editor: New York magazine, October 5, 1970.
  - Item 2: Soule Food, 1970; Publication (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Notes: Letter to the Editor: New York magazine, October 5, 1970. Copy 2.
- The Strike: For and Against, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Strike: For and Against, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 16)
    Author: Victor Gotbaum; Henry Hazlitt; Will Herberg; Paul Jennings; Theodore Kheel; Lewis Kaden; Merwin Lewis; Eugene McCarthy; Vincent McDonnell; Carey McWilliams; Victor Riesel; Robert Walsh
    Notes: A vital discussion of one of the prime issues of our day.
- The Taylor Law: A Critical Examination of Its Virtues and Defects, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Taylor Law: A Critical Examination of Its Virtues and Defects, 1968; Publication (Box 10, Folder 17)
    Notes: Reprint from Syracuse Law Review, v.20:no.2 (1968:Winter)
- Teaching in America, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Teaching in America, 1967; Publication (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Author: National Committee for Support of Public Schools
    Notes: Proceedings of the 5th Annual Conference, April 2-4, 1967.
- Technological Change and Human Development, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Technological Change and Human Development: An International Conference, Jerusalem, 1969, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: Introduction by Theodore W. Kheel
  - Item 2: Technological Change and Human Development: An International Conference, Jerusalem, 1969, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: Introduction by Theodore W. Kheel. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: Technological Change and Human Development: An International Conference, Jerusalem, 1969, Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: Introduction by Theodore W. Kheel. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: What's in Your Future?, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Author: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
    Notes: Flyer announcing the publication of "Technological Change and Human Development"
  - Item 5: What's in Your Future?, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: Flyer announcing the publication of "Technological Change and Human Development". Copy 2.
  - Item 6: What's in Your Future?, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 19)
    Notes: Flyer announcing the publication of "Technological Change and Human Development". Copy 3.
- Ted Kheel: Why I Won't Run, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Ted Kheel: Why I Won't Run, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Author: Manhattan Tribune
    Notes: v.1:no.19 (1969:Mar. 22)
  - Item 2: Ted Kheel: Why I Won't Run, 1969; Publication (Box 10, Folder 20)
    Notes: v.1:no.19 (1969:Mar. 22). Copy 2.
- The Ten Most Powerful Men in New York, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: The Ten Most Powerful Men in New York, 1971; Publication (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Author: Dick Schaap; Charlotte Curtis
    Notes: Published v.4:no.1 (1971:Jan. 4)
- Today's Man of Leisure, 1960; Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Today's Man of Leisure, 1960; Publication (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Author: Esquire
    Notes: Based upon the Esquire Subscribers' Leaisure Activities Study
- Tour of Duty, 2004; Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Tour of Duty: John Kerry and the Vietnam War, 2004; Publication (Box 10, Folder 23)